Register of the Friedrich A. von Hayek papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Incremental Materials IV, 1889-2005
  - Digital Files, 1989-2003 (Reading room workstation)
    - Disk 86002_023, 2003
      Original File Structure on Disk: MRSH_77.pdf MRSH_-77.pdf MRSH_78.pdf MRSH_79.pdf MRSH_80.pdf MRSH_81.pdf MRSH_82.pdf MRSH_83.pdf MRSH_84.pdf MRSH_85.pdf MRSH_86.pdf MRSH_87.pdf MRSH_88.pdf MRSH_89.pdf MRSH_90.pdf MRSH_91.pdf MRSH_92.pdf MRSH2.pdf MRSHGEN.pdf
    - Disk 86002_024, 1995
      Disk Label: H LETTS 77-87 H LETTS 83 84 85 87
      Original File Structure on Disk: HLETTS_77.pdf HLETTS_78.pdf HLETTS_79.pdf HLETTS_80.pdf HLETTS_81.pdf HLETTS_82.pdf HLETTS_83.pdf HLETTS_84.pdf HLETTS_85.pdf HLETTS_86.pdf HLETTS_87.pdf HLETTS_88.pdf HLETTS_89.pdf HLETTS_90.pdf HLETTS_91.pdf
    - Disk 86002_025, 1991-1995
      The files consist of notes and correspondence related to lectures, and Law, Legislation, and Liberty.
      Disk Label: H BIOG. KRESGE.91- LLL
      Original File Structure on Disk: KRESLETS STEPHEN_90.pdf STEPHEN_92.pdf STEPHEN_91.pdf STEPHEN_93.pdf L.pdf LECTURES.pdf LECTURES_77.pdf LEUBE_78.pdf LEUBE_83.pdf LEUBE_84.pdf LEUBE_85.pdf LEUBE_86.pdf LEUBE_87.pdf LEUBE_88.pdf LEUBE_89.pdf LEUBE_90.pdf LEUBE_91.pdf LEUBE_92.pdf LEUBE_TO_82.pdf LLL.pdf
    - Disk 86002_026, 1992-1995
      Disk Label: H LETTS 82 H BIOG HOLS - KRESGE.91
      Original File Structure on Disk: FIRNBERG.pdf HOLS.pdf HOLS_SEE.pdf HOOVER.pdf HOPPMANN.pdf I.pdf ICUS_79.pdf ICUS_83.pdf ICUS_85.pdf ICUS_86.pdf ICUS_87.pdf ICUS_89.pdf ICUS_90.pdf ICUS_91.pdf ICUS_92.pdf ITEM_93.pdf J.pdf JAPAN.pdf JOURNEYS.pdf JOURNEYS_77.pdf K.pdf KEY1.pdf KEY2.pdf
    - Disk 86002_027, 1989-1990
      The files consist of notes and correspondence related to Hayek's daily activities, William Bartley, and drafts of The Fatal Conceit and autobiographical writings.
      Disk Label: BARTLETS 77, 88, 89, 90 FC 11, 12, 14, 15 [crossed out] FC FC FOOTNOTE SII [crossed out] H DIARY 88 (1-12), H MEMOIR [crossed out] 187.392 H MEMOIRS
      Original File Structure on Disk: _DIARY.88 _1_88.pdf _2_88.pdf _0_88.pdf _88.pdf HMEMOIR 14_18.pdf 15_19.pdf 16_35.pdf 17_13.pdf 18_12.pdf 19_14.pdf 20_20.pdf 21_21.pdf 22_22.pdf 23_23.pdf 24_24.pdf 25_25.pdf 26_26.pdf 27_27.pdf 28_28.pdf 29_57.pdf 30_58.pdf 31_30.pdf 32_36.pdf 33_1.pdf 34_32.pdf 35_33.pdf 36_34.pdf 37_31.pdf 38_8.pdf 39_37.pdf 40_42.pdf 41_43.pdf 42_40.pdf 43_41.pdf 44_38.pdf 45_38B.pdf 46_53.pdf 47_51.pdf 48_52.pdf 49_39.pdf 50_45.pdf 51_44.pdf 52_7.pdf 53_47.pdf 54_46.pdf 55_48.pdf 56_49.pdf 57_9B.pdf 58_6.pdf 59_50.pdf 60_55.pdf 61_56.pdf 62_2.pdf KEY.pdf 1_54.pdf 2_29.pdf 3_53B.pdf 4_3.pdf 5_55B.pdf 6_5.pdf 7_4.pdf 8_11.pdf 9_8B.pdf 10_9.pdf 11_15.pdf 12_16.pdf 13_17.pdf BILL_77.pdf BILL_78.pdf BILL_79.pdf BILL_80.pdf BILL_81.pdf BILL_82.pdf BILL_83.pdf BILL_84.pdf BILL_85.pdf BILL_86.pdf BILL_87.pdf BILL_88.pdf BILL_89.pdf BILL_90.pdf FC_11.pdf FC_13.pdf FC_14.pdf FC_15.pdf FCNOTES_11.pdf
    - Disk 86002_028, 1995
      Disk Label: PPWIN [crossed out] (2) BARTLEY LETTS
      Original File Structure on Disk: PPWIN PPWIN BAR184E.pdf BAR187B.pdf BAR239A.pdf BAR287B.pdf BAR387.pdf BAR485.pdf BAR487.pdf BAR685B.pdf BAR784D.pdf BAR785B.pdf BAR787.pdf BAR884D.pdf BAR887.pdf BAR987B.pdf BAR987C.pdf CL484D.pdf CL684C.pdf CL784E.pdf CL784L.pdf CL785H.pdf CL787B.pdf CL787E.pdf CL787H.pdf CL885B.pdf CL984.pdf CN785.pdf COMPC95.pdf FIN784.pdf HL485.pdf HL784E.pdf HL787.pdf BAR185B.pdf BAR285B.pdf BAR285E.pdf CL385B.pdf HFAM385.pdf HFAM385B.pdf PUB285B.pdf PUB285D.pdf PUB285E.pdf MOR187.pdf MORR175.pdf PUB384.pdf PUB585.pdf PUB787B.pdf PUB985.pdf BAR387E.pdf BAR685D.pdf BAR785D.pdf BAR785F.pdf BAR785H.pdf BAR785J.pdf BAR885C.pdf BAR985E.pdf BAR1084C.pdf BAR1084G.pdf BAR1084I.pdf BAR1085A.pdf BAR1085C.pdf BAR1087C.pdf BAR1284.pdf BAR1287B.pdf BAR1985E.pdf CL9.pdf CL684.pdf CL787.pdf CL787G.pdf CL787I.pdf CL884E.pdf CL1087.pdf FC287.pdf FC687.pdf FC887C.pdf FURT1287.pdf GRAMM.pdf HFAM584.pdf HFAM1085.pdf HGAM684.pdf HL784C.pdf HL785.pdf HL787B.pdf HL987A.pdf ICUS1085.pdf LASKI384.pdf MORR487.pdf MRSH785B.pdf PUB187.pdf PUB284.pdf SPEAR384.pdf THER685C.pdf BAR385B.pdf BAR387B.pdf BAR585C.pdf BAR784C.pdf BAR787B.pdf BAR884C.pdf BAR887B.pdf CL287.pdf CL485.pdf CL787F.pdf CL884C.pdf COMPB95.pdf COLL1287.pdf HL784.pdf FC787B.pdf PUB587.pdf HL784F.pdf PUB385.pdf PUB1084.pdf MRSH785D.pdf MORR2010.pdf BAR1285.pdf BAR184.pdf HFA1085B.pdf CL787D.pdf HOPP1285.pdf MOR1087B.pdf BAR887C.pdf PUB887B.pdf BAR385.pdf CL784.pdf HFA1085D.pdf BAR285C.pdf BAR385C.pdf MOR1087A.pdf BAR885.pdf CL385E.pdf BAR184C.pdf BAR1084E.pdf HFAM1285.pdf BAR185.pdf FC787.pdf CL885E.pdf PUB387B.pdf HFAM385C.pdf BAR285.pdf CL984B.pdf BAR485B.pdf BAR1187A.pdf PBU985.pdf SPEAR2.pdf BAR985.pdf C.pdf CL385.pdf CL484B.pdf BAR884F.pdf BAR1O87A.pdf CL785F.pdf BAR984.pdf PUBS711.pdf BAR585.pdf HFAM784.pdf BAT1187B.pdf BAT1185C.pdf BAR684B.pdf CL785I.pdf BAR987.pdf BAR1187.pdf MRS785B.pdf BAR1185D.pdf HAR584.pdf CL385C.pdf CL784F.pdf PUB184B.pdf BAR1087D.pdf BAT1085D.pdf BAR687.pdf BAR1185B.pdf ROMPC95.pdf FC887.pdf HL885B.pdf BAR585D.pdf THER685.pdf ROMPA95.pdf BAR887D.pdf BETH885B.pdf CL784C.pdf BAR187.pdf HL385.pdf CL787J.pdf PUB1184.pdf BAR1085E.pdf PUB787.pdf BAR985B.pdf BAR387C.pdf BAR1087B.pdf BAR1287C.pdf BAR1287A.pdf BAR784.pdf CHINA984.pdf HFAM187.pdf BAR1087.pdf CL184.pdf BAR1187B.pdf BAR1084.pdf BAR187D.pdf CL385D.pdf CL785.pdf CL787C.pdf FC587.pdf BAR985C.pdf PUB285C.pdf PUB285.pdf BAR884.pdf MOR484.pdf FUR1085.pdf FC887B.pdf BAR285D.pdf BAR385E.pdf CL784H.pdf CL885C.pdf FC587B.pdf PUB887.pdf FIN885.pdf HL987.pdf BAR1087C.pdf BAR1284.pdf BAR387.pdf BAR387B.pdf BAR985E.pdf BAR987C.pdf CL9.pdf CL884C.pdf COMPB95.pdf HFAM1085.pdf HL787_001.pdf BAR784D.pdf PUB385.pdf BAR184F.pdf BAR484.pdf BAR187C.pdf BAR685.pdf BAR785G.pdf BAR1185E.pdf BAT584.pdf FURT1287.pdf CL787G.pdf HL1085.pdf MORR487.pdf MRSH785.pdf PUB187B.pdf CL484.pdf CL784G.pdf HFAM1285_SEE.pdf BAR184E.pdf BAR187_002.pdf BAR387E.pdf BAR
    - Disk 86002_029, 1995-2000
      The files consist of notes and correspondence related to William Bartley.
      Disk Label: BARTLEY 85 86 87
      Original File Structure on Disk: Bartley_85.pdf Bartley_86.pdf Bartley_87.pdf
    - Disk 86002_030, 1999
      The files consist of notes and correspondence related to The Fatal Conceit.
      Disk Label: FACTAL CONCEIT ICUS HOOVER
      Original File Structure on Disk: Fatal_Conceit.pdf Hoover.pdf ICUS.pdf
    - Disk 86002_031, 1989-1995
      The files consist of notes and correspondence related to Collected Works and the Walter Eucken Institut.
      Disk Label: H BIOG. COLLWKS.84 - FC.84 [crossed out] FANS BARTLETS [crossed out]
      Original File Structure on Disk: COLLWKS_84.pdf COLLWKS_85.pdf COLLWKS_86.pdf COLLWKS_87.pdf COLLWKS_88.pdf COLLWKS_89.pdf COLLWKS_90.pdf COLLWKS_91.pdf COLLWKS_92.pdf DAMS.pdf DEATH.pdf DOCUMTS.pdf E.pdf EUCKEN_77.pdf EUCKEN_-77.pdf EUCKEN_78.pdf EUCKEN_79.pdf EUCKEN_80.pdf EUCKEN_81.pdf EUCKEN_82.pdf EUCKEN_83.pdf EUCKEN_84.pdf EUCKEN_85.pdf EUCKEN_86.pdf EUCKEN_87.pdf EUCKEN_88.pdf EUCKEN_89.pdf EUCKEN_90.pdf EUCKEN_91.pdf EUCKEN_92.pdf F.pdf FANS.pdf
    - Disk 86002_032, 1993-1995
      Disk Label: FC.
      Original File Structure on Disk: FC_78.pdf FC_79.pdf FC_80.pdf FC_81.pdf FC_82.pdf FC_83.pdf FC_84.pdf FC_85.pdf FC_86.pdf FC_87.pdf FC_88.pdf FC_89.pdf FC_90.pdf FC_91.pdf
    - Disk 86002_033, 1989-1993
      The files consist of notes and correspondence related to Hayek's publications and their translation into other languages.
      Disk Label: BY - H (ALSO NEW & OLD [crossed out] H FOLDERS [crossed out] RTS [crossed out] TRS [crossed out] BYH ABOUT - H [crossed out] 19.456 [crossed out] 10/1/03
      Original File Structure on Disk: BY-H _980S.pdf _OTESFC_11.pdf 1920.pdf 1930.pdf 1940.pdf 1950.pdf 1960.pdf 1970.pdf 1980.pdf 1990.pdf HODDS.pdf NEW.pdf FOLDERS BR1.pdf BR2.pdf BR3.pdf FILCAB.pdf I.pdf II.pdf III.pdf IV.pdf IX.pdf TAPES.pdf V.pdf VI.pdf VII.pdf VIII.pdf X.pdf XA.pdf XI.pdf XII.pdf XIII.pdf RTS CZECH.pdf FINNISH.pdf FRENCH.pdf GEN.pdf GREEK.pdf INDIAN.pdf JAPANESE.pdf KEY.pdf NAMES.pdf SPANISH.pdf SWEDISH.pdf TRS ARABIC.pdf CHINESE.pdf CZECH.pdf DANISH.pdf DUTCH.pdf FRENCH.pdf GERMAN.pdf HUNGARY.pdf ICELAND.pdf INDIAN.pdf ITALIAN.pdf JAPAN.pdf KOREAN.pdf MALAYAN.pdf NORWAY.pdf PERSIAN.pdf POLISH.pdf PORTUGAL.pdf ROMANIAN.pdf RUSSIAN.pdf SERBCROT.pdf SPANISH.pdf SWEDISH.pdf 1920S.pdf 1930S.pdf 1940S.pdf 1950S.pdf 1960S.pdf 1980S.pdf ABOUT_H.pdf KEY1.pdf KEY2.pdf NEW.pdf OLD.pdf
    - Disk 86002_034, 1998
      The files consist of notes and correspondence related to the Cato Insitute.
      Disk Label: CATO foundtell [illegible] WSWIN2 [crossed out] 4 [crossed out] HFIN.85
      Original File Structure on Disk: CATO.pdf
    - Disk 86002_035, 1993-1995
      The files consist of notes and correspondence related to William Bartley and various other topics.
      Disk Label: H BIOG. A - BARTELY.87 81 - 84
      Original File Structure on Disk: A.pdf ADDRESS.pdf AUSTRIA.pdf B.pdf BARTLEY_60S.pdf BARTLEY_70S.pdf Bartley_81_81.pdf BARTLEY_82.pdf BARTLEY_83.pdf Bartley_84_84.pdf
    - Disk 86002_036, 1990-1995
      Disk Label: H BIOG. S - WORK 81
      Original File Structure on Disk: S.pdf SCH.pdf SHENOY.pdf SOUTH_AM.pdf SPEECH.pdf T.pdf TEST.pdf THATCHER.pdf U.pdf V.pdf VISA.pdf W.pdf WOMEN.pdf WORK_77.pdf WORK_78.pdf WORK_79.pdf WORK_80.pdf WORK_81.pdf
    - Disk 86002_037, 1999
      The files consist of notes and correspondence related to travel, Helene von Hayek, and Hayek's views on women.
      Disk Label: MRS. HAYEK WOMEN JOURNEYS
      Original File Structure on Disk: Mrs_Hayek.pdf Women.pdf Journeys.pdf
    - Disk 86002_038, 1990-1995
      The files consist of general notes and correspondence and correspondence between members of the Hayek family.
      Disk Label: H LETTERS MA-ZI FAMLETS: HAYEKS 4.90, 88-92, 92 SEI PUBLISERS, FOREIGN 89.088
      Original File Structure on Disk: HAMLETS _90.pdf _AYEKS_92.pdf _LETTS_77.pdf 79.pdf 80.pdf 81.pdf 82.pdf 83.pdf 84.pdf 85.pdf 86.pdf 87.pdf 88.pdf 89.pdf 90.pdf 90_90.pdf 91.pdf 92.pdf MA.pdf ME.pdf MO.pdf MONTP.pdf MU.pdf NE.pdf NI.pdf NO.pdf O.pdf OB.pdf OP.pdf OX.pdf PA.pdf PCASH.pdf PE.pdf PI.pdf PO.pdf PR.pdf Q.pdf R^.pdf RA.pdf RE.pdf RI.pdf RO.pdf RU.pdf SA.pdf SC.pdf SH.pdf SI.pdf SM.pdf SO.pdf SZ.pdf TH.pdf THATCHER_92.pdf TO.pdf V.pdf WA.pdf WE.pdf WH.pdf WI.pdf WO.pdf WU.pdf ZA.pdf ZI.pdf
    - Disk 86002_039, 1997-2003
      Disk Label: HAYEK I LETTS. A-I HAY MEM
      Original File Structure on Disk: Gräf.pdf Harris.pdf HayekPapers.pdf Hayeks.pdf Haymem.pdf Hennings.pdf Hennings_96.pdf Hennings_97.pdf Hoferichter.pdf Hoover.pdf Hoppmann.pdf IEA.pdf AustrianEmbassy.pdf BBC.pdf Blundell.pdf Bosch.pdf Crowley.pdf Dataprot.pdf Diamond.pdf Dietzel.pdf Ebenstein.pdf Eucken.pdf Fawcett.pdf FreiburgUni.pdf Furth.pdf Garbass.pdf Gown.pdf